wmnlife.com 2019-03-19

# Cookies policy

##  Privacy and Cookies policy 

**PRIVACY POLICY AT A GLANCE**  
WMNLife (also referred to as we, us, our) are 100% committed to protecting the privacy and security of individuals (also referred to as you, users, visitors). This Privacy notice only applies to wmnlife.com website and not to any other services/websites that we may own. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by us. Please read the following to understand about our privacy practices. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.   
This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what information we collect, why we collect it, how we use it, for how long we store it and how you can manage or delete your information.  
WMNLife takes your privacy seriously and is committed to protecting your privacy rights. We and our employees understand the need for user privacy, and we maintain reasonable and appropriate security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. You always have the right to review the personal information we keep about you filling the form below.  
We can only speak for ourselves so this policy doesn't cover the collection or use of your information by any of the third party services. When you use or interact with the wmnlife.com we and third parties integrated into our website may obtain certain information about you. This information could be processed by them in accordance with their own privacy policy and terms and conditions. We do not sell or rent your personal data.   
You'll come across the term "personal data" a lot in this policy. By that, we mean any information relating to you as an identifiable individual. For example, this includes information that may of itself identify you such as your internet protocol ("IP") address, cookie strings or device IDs, as well as information that may not on its own identify you, but which we store alongside such identifiers, such as how you are using our services or the country you are in when you do so.  
We’ll review this policy from time to time to make sure it's up-to-date. If we make changes, we'll post the latest version here. 

**PRIVACY POLICY (EFFECTIVE FROM MAY 25, 2018)**   
This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of WMNLife only and does not cover the practices of other companies, including those that may advertise or sponsor content, products or services on the wmnlife.com. WMNLife (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its visitors and users of this website (the “Site”). We created this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate a commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy.   
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how we treat information that you provide to us or that we collect about you. By "Personal Data", we refer to data that relates to you as an identified or identifiable natural person. The term “Personal Data” may include name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, age, IP address etc. Anonymous information, which we are not in a position to relate to you, does not qualify as "Personal Data". 

**COLLECTION OF GENERAL DATA AND INFORMATION**  
We collect personal information in order to provide useful content and follow up on its effectiveness for marketing purposes. Our advertising partners collect information about your behavior on our Site in order to deliver interest-based advertising on our behalf. We do not share any personal information with these partners, but you may have shared information with them if you have signed up for any of their services (such as Google, Taboola, Facebook etc). We may also collect information to prevent and detect crime, fraud or corruption. We may process and share your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations when we use your information to protect our rights or the rights of others and when we share your information with other parties where required by law or as necessary to protect our rights.   
When you use a Site, we may obtain various types of information related to you and your use of the Site.  In relation to your use of our Site, we gather information either directly from you (when you provide information to us) or indirectly (e.g. through our Site’s technology).

 **INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US**  
We may collect and store information that you voluntarily supply to us while using our Site, including information you send to us by email (and other platforms in connection with a feature provided through the Site) or submit your information to us using the “Contact Us” form. This may include information that can be used to contact or identify you, such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone numbers, birthdate and gender. As an example of this type: information that you electronically submit when you contact us with questions. Unless a person voluntarily submits personal data to us (for example, by sending us an e-mail or completing the contact form), we cannot personally identify an individual. By submitting a form on our Site, you confirm that you have read and accept this privacy policy, and that you understand that data will be collected and processed for the purposes outlined in this policy.  If you do not want your Personal Information collected, please do not submit it.

 **INFORMATION THAT IS AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED**  
We collect and store information that is generated automatically as you use our Site. This general data and information are stored in the server log files. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information and calls pseudonymous information. Some examples of this type of information include:

  * the browser types and versions used
  * the operating system used by the accessing system
  * type of device or computer used
  * the website from which an accessing system reaches our Site (so-called referrers)
  * exit pages to other websites
  * the date and time of access to the Site
  * information on the usage of our Site such as time spent on each page, clicks on a page, downloads, etc.
  * an Internet protocol address (IP address), which may be used to derive your general geographic area (e.g., city and country).
  * the Internet service provider of the accessing system (ISP)
  * any other similar data and information that may be used in the event of attacks on our information technology systems.

We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie" to enhance your experience with our Site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your Device for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique users visit us, and track user trends and patterns. If you want to know more about our Cookies policy please read more below.  
We also may use web beacons (single-pixel graphic files also known as "transparent GIFs") to access cookies and to count users who use the Site. We may assign an anonymous identifier to the tracking pixel or session cookie. In addition, a pixel tag may tell your browser to get content from another server. Also we use tracking codes to find out more about how you interact with our services, the adverts you see and more generally, how you use us. Tracking codes are snippets of code placed in the page to measure things like visits and interactions.  
We may also use third party vendors who collect information regarding your online activities through their own cookies, web beacons, and other technologies either on our Site and/or other websites across the Internet, in an effort to understand your interests and deliver you advertisements that are tailored to your interests.  
The data collected in connection with the ad serving, performance analyzing ad targeting through our Site does not include your name, postal address, email address or telephone number unless you affirmatively provide information within the ad. However, it may include Device identifying information such as the IP address, MAC address, cookie or other Device-specific unique ID. These service providers also may assign an anonymous identifier to the tracking pixel or session cookie.  
The collection of information by our service providers and third-party advertising service providers is governed by their relevant privacy notices, for which we have no responsibility or liability, and are not covered by our Privacy Notice. If you have any questions regarding the privacy notice of one of our service providers, you should contact the service provider directly for more information.  
We may use third party analytics vendors to evaluate and provide us with information about the use of the Service. We do not share Personal Information with these third parties, but they may set and access their own cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, including Usage Information. We use Google Analytics to analyze the performance of our Site and follow up on the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. Google Analytics allow us to analyze data in aggregate, we do not collect or store any personal information in Google Analytics. Please note that one of our third-party advertising service providers is Google Adsense, read Google’s services privacy policy here - https://policies.google.com/privacy  
We may also use third party content networks that use redirects (like Taboola, you can read their Privacy Policy here - https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy), which will redirect you through a third party server before redirecting to the final landing page. On this redirect, the third party may place its own cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies on your device (e.g., for purposes of retargeting) and collect or have access to information about you, including Usage Information.  
If you would like more information about the information collection practices of a particular third-party advertising service provider, or if you would like more information on how to opt out of a third-party advertising service provider’s information collection practices, go to www.aboutads.info, or for apps, at www.aboutads.info/appchoices

 **HOW WE USE INFORMATION**  
When using these general data and information, we do not draw any conclusions about the data subject. Rather, this information is needed to:  
deliver the content of our Site correctly  
optimize the content of our Site as well as its advertisement  
ensure the long-term viability of our information technology systems and Site technology  
respond to your request  
provide law enforcement authorities with the information necessary for criminal prosecution in case of a cyber-attack.   
Therefore, we analyze anonymously collected data and information statistically, with the aim of increasing the data protection and data security of our Site, and to ensure an optimal level of protection for the personal data we process. The anonymous data of the server log files are stored separately from all personal data provided by a data subject. We cannot tell who you are unless you willingly identify yourself on our Site. If you at some point have identified yourself by filling out a form on our Site, pages you view on our Site may be connected to your personal information. We do this to understand the effectiveness of our Site. We never sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We may use location information, either information you provided by you or information automatically collected, in order to provide you with location-based content, interest-based content services and advertising. We also may combine information we collect from you while you are using our Site with information that we collect from other sources, including other websites or apps, to customize features, content and advertising that appear through our Site.   
The data we collect helps us to:

  * understand topics of interest
  * understand trends
  * understand Site usage and engagement
  * understand visitor profiles e.g. geographical
  * develop advertising and marketing campaigns, promotions and offers.

We use the collected data to:

  * improve our Site design and content
  * run A/B tests that display alternate versions of our Site to different groups of users.

**HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**  
We may share aggregated or pseudonymous information (including demographic information) with partners, such as publishers, advertisers, measurement analytics, apps, or other companies.  For example, we may tell an advertiser how its ads performed. We do not share information that personally identifies you (personally identifiable information is information like name or email address) with these partners.  
When you use third-party apps, websites or other products integrated with our Services, they may collect information about your activities subject to their own terms and privacy policies.  
We allow other companies that show advertisements on our Site to collect information from your browsers or devices. Other companies' use of cookies and other data collection technologies are subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Like many companies, we may allow cookie matching with select partners. But, these parties are not authorized to access ours cookies.  
We may disclose Personal Information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of this Site, the Service or the public.. We may also disclose your Personal Information to outside individuals and/or companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer and to create, operate, and maintain our Site. For example, we may work with third parties to:

  * to communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone, text message or other means about our company, our products, or other company’s
  * services, products or information that we believe may be of interest to you
  * manage a database of customer information
  * assist us with direct marketing, distributing e-mails and data collection
  * provide data storage and analysis
  * provide fraud prevention
  * provide customer service
  * provide other services designed to assist us in developing and running our Site and maximizing our business potential.

We require that these outside companies agree to keep all information shared with them confidential and to use the information only to perform their obligations to us.  
In addition, if we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred.  
We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information and Usage Information with third parties. We may combine your Usage Information with those of other users of the Service in order to share trend information with third parties, always in aggregated and anonymized form. For example, we may use your Usage Information as part of an aggregated number to tell a prospective sponsor how many people visit sports our Site each month.  
We may share Personal Data with our affiliates, subsidiaries, vendors or agents working on our behalf for the purposes described in this Policy. For example, we may hire companies to assist with protecting and securing our systems or services. Any vendor or agent that we retain must comply with our data privacy and security requirements and are not allowed to use personal data they receive from us for any other purpose. Those companies may be located outside of the European Economic Area. 

**HOW WE STORE AND PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**  
Transmitting information over the internet is generally not completely secure. We have procedures and security in place to keep personal data secure once it is in our systems.  
We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we make reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
We will keep your personal information for as long as we have a relationship with you. Once our relationship with you has come to an end, we will retain your personal information for a period of time that enables us to:

  * Maintain business records for analysis, understanding market trends and/or audit purposes and to improve the Site
  * Comply with record retention requirements under applicable laws or other relevant legal or regulatory requirements
  * Defend, establish, exercise or bring any existing or potential legal claims
  * Carry out fraud detection and prevention
  * Deal with any complaints regarding the Site.

We will delete your personal information when it is no longer required for these purposes. If there is any information that we are unable, for technical reasons, to delete from our systems, we will put in place appropriate measures to prevent any further processing or use of the data.  
We store personal data in digital format on secure cloud servers and systems in the U.S. and our service providers may be located there and in other countries. By providing us personal information, you agree that your personal information may be transferred to and stored in these countries. These countries may have different and/or less stringent privacy/data protection and data security rules than those of your own country. As a result, your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those countries according to laws in those countries. Subject to the applicable laws in such other countries, we will provide the necessary safeguards to maintain protections of your personal information, e.g. by obtaining from the data recipients contractual commitments based on the EU model clauses.  
Access to personal data is highly restricted internally for approved business purposes only. We keep your personal data only for as long as we need to. This depends on why it was collected, or if we have a continuing legal basis to do so (such as to fulfill a contract between us, perform a service you requested or for our legitimate interests). Rest assured, if we no longer have a reason or legal requirement to process your personal data, we will delete it or store it in a way so that it no longer identifies you.

 **HOW YOU CAN OPT OUT OF WEB TRACKING**  
There are several ways to opt out of web tracking:  
Most browsers allow you to block third-party cookies or prevent cross-domain tracking. This will limit the cookies that can be set by third-party scripts. This will not completely eliminate tracking by some third-party services though as they may use first-party cookies. Most browsers also allow you ask not to be tracked (it sends the “Do Not Track” request header). If you have enabled this feature, we will not track the pages you visit in a way that enables us to connect them to your personal information. Your page views may still be collected anonymously though. Many of the third-party services we use for collecting anonymous data also respect the Do Not Track setting.  
You can opt out of interest-based advertising on these two pages: NAI consumer opt-out page - http://optout.networkadvertising.org/ and DAA opt-out page - http://optout.aboutads.info/. This will not remove ads, but will for example remove the possibility for us to display ads to people that have visited our Site. Note that these services in themselves requires cookies. You can also opt out from the individual services we use:

  * AdRoll: You can turn off interest-based ads on AdRoll’s opt-out page - https://app.adroll.com/optout/safari
  * Facebook: You can turn off interest-based ads in your Facebook settings – please see this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217
  * Google ads, including Google AdWords, Google AdSense and Doubleclick: You can turn of personalization for Google’s display and search ads – please see this page: You can edit your settings for ad personalization here - https://adssettings.google.com/.There is more information on ad personalization on Google and through their ad networks here - https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922
  * Google Analytics: You can use Google’s opt-out browser add-on to prevent tracking in Google Analytics, see https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
  * Microsoft (including Bing): You can turn off interest-based ads here: https://choice.microsoft.com/
  * Optimizely: If you want to opt out of Optimizely experiments (such as A/B-testing), please follow the instructions on this page - https://www.optimizely.com/legal/opt-out/

**YOUR RIGHTS AS AN INDIVIDUAL BASED IN THE EU**

  * Access to your information: You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you.
  * Correcting your information: We want to have accurate data. Please contact us if you think the data we hold is not up to date or correct.
  * Deletion of your information: You have the right to ask us to delete Personal Data about you if it no longer is required for the purpose it was collected, you have withdrawn your consent, you have a valid objection to us using your Personal Data, or our use of your Personal Data is contrary to law or our other legal obligations.
  * Objecting to how we may use your information: You have the right at any time to require us to stop using your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes.
  * Please contact if you wish to exercise any of these rights. You can find the contact details below.

**CHILDREN**  
We recognize that we have a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from children. The Site is not intended for use by children, especially those under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we determine upon collection that a user is under 13, we will not use or maintain his/her Personal Information without the parent/guardian’s consent. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records.

 **LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**  
Our Site also include links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control and for which we have no responsibility or liability. When you access another website or purchase products or services from a third-party, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy notice of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these sites or their content, products, services or privacy policies or practices.

 **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
We keep this Privacy policy under review and may update it at any time. Any updates will be made on this page so that you can always find out what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we will disclose it. The Privacy policy was last updated May 25, 2018.

 **HOW TO CONTACT US**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mailing us at [privacy@wmnlife.com](mailto:privacy@wmnlife.com)

 **COOKIES POLICY**   
A cookie is a small piece of text sent to your browser by a website you visit. It helps the website to remember information about your visit, like your preferred language and other settings. That can make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. Cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more frustrating experience.  
We use cookies for performance and analytics purposes: We use our own cookies and/or third-party cookies and other identifiers (such as web beacons) to see how you use our websites and services in order to enhance their performance and develop them according to the preferences of our customers and visitors. For example, cookies and web beacons may be used to: test different designs and to ensure that we maintain a consistent look and feel across our websites; recognize repeat visitors, track and provide trend analysis on how our users interact with our websites and communications; track errors and measure the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. The data collected will generally be aggregated to provide trends and usage patterns for business analysis, site/platform improvement and performance metrics and to inform our advertising and marketing strategies. Our cookies, or the resulting analysis, may also be shared with our business partners. We may also receive similar information about visitors to our group company and other partner websites.  
We use the following categories of cookies for our website and Services:

  * Strictly Necessary Cookies  
These cookies are essential in order to enable you to navigate our website and use its features.
  * Performance Cookies  
These cookies collect anonymous information on how people use our website. For example, we use these cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our site, browse or use our site and highlight areas where we can improve, such as navigation and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.
  * Functionality Cookies  
These cookies remember choices you make such as the country from which you visit our website, language and search parameters such as size, color or product line. These cookies can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate to your selections and to make the visits more tailored and relevant. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
  * Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies  
These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. The cookies remember the websites you visit and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers. Please see our Interest-Based Advertising section below for information about your choices regarding our use of these technologies for interest-based advertising.

Publishers, advertisers and third-party ad networks may also utilize cookies or similar technologies to deliver ads and monitor the performance of such ads. The collection of information through cookies or similar technologies by such third parties will be governed by their own privacy policies and principles, which we do not control.  
Your browser may offer tools to enable or disable cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, please note that certain features of the  website may not work if you delete or disable cookies.   
We measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. All of that information is pseudonymous – so we don’t know who you are; just that somebody visited our site. The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better. We use the following Google Optimize cookies, which are used to determine your inclusion in an experiment (e.g. an A/B test on button colours our users prefer, which we use for UX improvement of our interfaces) and the expiry of experiments a user has been included in. The cookies expire after 50 month.  
You can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Further information can be found under http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html (Google Analytics Terms of Service & Privacy). You can learn more about Google Privacy Policy here - http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html  
We may update this cookies policy from time-to-time, particularly as technology changes. You can always check this page for the latest version.  
The Cookies Policy was last updated May 25, 2018
